{
  "type": "flashcards",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "位",
      "answer": "Wèi | a polite measure word for persons"
    },
    {
      "question": "车",
      "answer": "Chē | vehicle"
    },
    {
      "question": "电脑",
      "answer": "Diànnǎo | computer"
    },
    {
      "question": "词典",
      "answer": "Cídiǎn | dictioanry"
    },
    {
      "question": "孩子",
      "answer": "Háizi | child"
    },
    {
      "question": "助教",
      "answer": "Zhùjiào | teaching assistant"
    },
    {
      "question": "系主任",
      "answer": "Xì zhǔrèn | director of the department"
    },
    {
      "question": "律师",
      "answer": "Lǜshī | laywer"
    },
    {
      "question": "工程师",
      "answer": "Gōngchéngshī | engineer"
    },
    {
      "question": "爷爷",
      "answer": "Yéyé | paternal grandfather"
    },
    {
      "question": "外公",
      "answer": "Wàigōng | maternal grandfather"
    },
    {
      "question": "年",
      "answer": "Nián | year"
    },
    {
      "question": "前",
      "answer": "Qián | ago"
    },
    {
      "question": "英语",
      "answer": "Yīngyǔ | English"
    },
    {
      "question": "常常",
      "answer": "Chángcháng | often"
    },
  ]
}
